{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5394","name":"Ima","address":"2015 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216","owner":"Eighty Ate LLC","licenseNumber":"209341","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.07389,42.33115","geojson":{"id":"5394","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.073889282,42.331152219]},"properties":{"name":"Ima","owner":"Eighty Ate LLC","address":"2015 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"209341","establishmentid":"5394","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/3/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622820","name":"Lucky Detroit Coffee & Espresso","address":"2000 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"284","name":"L J'S Sweetheart bar","address":"2114 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51622645","name":"Grandma Bobs Pizza","address":"2135 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4300","name":"Sugar House","address":"2130 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"2950","name":"Slows BBQ","address":"2138 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"3745","name":"Mercury Burger Bar","address":"2163 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"408","name":"Maltese Am Benevolent Society","address":"1832 Michigan Avenue","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","address":"1830 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"1932","name":"Hernandez Center Head Start","address":"2051 Rosa Parks Blvd, Ste. 1K","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51622463","name":"Corktown Tavern Inc.","address":"1716 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44261","inspectionDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"shelving dry storage","problemDescription":"Bare wood","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Storage shelves","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace/seal to be smooth, durable, non-absorbent, and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Wall (back)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"43708","inspectionDate":"2018-10-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42491","inspectionDate":"2018-06-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Wall (west)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Exhaust fan","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40934","inspectionDate":"2017-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"40932","inspectionDate":"2017-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"39022","inspectionDate":"2017-06-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Single-service items","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"On the bottom Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"Laying on prep table or cooking equipment Without approved written procedure for cleaning & sanitizing","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store as stated above."}]},{"inspectionid":"37624","inspectionDate":"2017-01-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Hair Restraints/Covering","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"37218","inspectionDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"No Product stem thermometer(s)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"No Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the UNNECESSARY ITEMS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-03-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5394"}}